Let's take a look at how we might do a couple of these things in real practice.
让我们来看看如何在实践环境中做这些事情
Okay, let's get down to coding.
Okay 让我们开始编写代码
So we have an HTML document here,
这里我们有一个 HTML 文件
and then I have that HTML document being red here in a Chrome browser.
现在我们在浏览器中打开这个文件
Right now, there's nothing to see because we haven't written any code.
当然 现在我们看不到内容 因为我们还没有编写任何代码
But, let's start by adding the h1 that we talked about earlier.
但是 让我们来添加一个之前提到的 h1 标签
You can see that there is a starting tag here and then a closing tag here,
你可以看到这里有一个开始标签和一个结束标签
and anything we put in between those will be our header.
我们可以在它们之间放置标题内容
So here I might say HTML is awesome, and that's it.
让我们在中间输入 HTML is awesome 好了
That's your first HTML element.
这就是你的一个 HTML 元素了
Now let's make sure I'm telling the truth here,
现在 我们来确认一下刚才说的有没有错
and boom, there it is.
砰 出现了
HTML is awesome.
HTML is awesome
So now let's see what would happen if we make
现在我们再来看看如果我们使用 p 标签
a paragraph which is the p tag and we say the same thing just to test it out.
我们放上相同的内容来测试它们
HTML is awesome, h1,
HTML is awesome, h1,
HTML is awesome in a paragraph tag.
HTML is awesome 放置在段落标签里
In our browser, you can see that the h1 tag
在浏览器中 你可以看见 同样文字的 h1 标签
with the same tax that's produced this giant bold headline.
显示为大号加粗标题
The paragraph text is here looking more like it would be in a paragraph,
而段落标签中的文字看起来就更像是段落文字
which is pretty awesome.
真是太酷了
But as I mentioned,
但是就像我提到的
sometimes we want to be even more creative and
有时候我们想要更有创意的效果
use text representation that isn't just built right in.
不只是使用内置的文本样式
So for that, we can use divs.
这样的话 我们可以使用 div
A div can have a starting and a closing tag just like everything
一个 div 可以和其它内容一样具有开始标签和结束标签
else and this is where we start to assign attributes.
也就是我们可以放置属性的地方
Any HTML element can have attributes,
一个 HTML 元素可以有属性
and the attributes will almost always go inside the opening tag.
属性几乎总是放置在开始标签里
An example here is to say I have a div and I want to give it the attribute an ID,
一个例子就是我有一个 div 然后我想在上面添加一个 ID 属性
and I'll say that this ID is unicorn.
然后我们设置 ID 为 unicorn
So here we have a div with the id unicorn and what do we want it to say?
这里我们已经有了一个 id 为 unicorn 的 div 你想让它显示什么内容呢？
Probably something about unicorns,
最好跟 unicorns 有关
it's hard to spell for something that's not real, unicorns.
这个词可真难拼写
All over the world sing songs of joy.
All over the world sing songs of joy.
So what do you think is going to happen when I refresh this?
现在 当我们刷新网页时会发生什么？
There it is, it looks an awful lot like our P tags.
看起来几乎和 p 标签一样
Pretty soon, we're going to learn how to use CSS to identify the attribute,
稍后 我们会学习如何通过 CSS 来识别属性
say the ID unicorn and then to set
例如 id unicorn
specific styling rules on specific elements using the attributes like ID.
然后使用它在特定元素上应用特殊的样式规则
We'll get to that later.
我们晚点再讨论它
For now, just think about the different ways
目前 只需知道你可以用不同的元素
you might use elements to lay out a web page.
来进行不同的布局
Like, what would happen if I moved this down to the bottom?
比如 如果我把它移动到下面会发生什么？
It shows up there on the browser too, very interesting.
它一样会显示在浏览器中 很有趣吧
Coming up next, we'll take a deeper dive into the elements that
接下来 我们会更深入地了解 HTML 提供的一些基础元素
HTML provides you with as your structure to build your foundation.
你可以用它们搭建网站的基础
I hope you're as excited as I am because pretty soon,
希望你会感到一点点激动
you'll be building to the skies digitally at least.
因为很快 你就可以尽情发挥了